(Howard:)All systems go,
if you catch my drift. Heh.
(Bernadette:)I always catch your drift.
(Howard:)Well, something's obviously
bugging you.
(Howard:)What is it?
I can't believe you signed up for
the space program without talking to me.
I get it. We...
You're worried about me.
(Howard:)That is so sweet. You know,
there's a saying we have at NASA.
(Howard:)What makes the right stuff so right
is that it always comes home.
(Bernadette:)Just stop talking, Howard.
(Howard:)This isn't the reaction I expected...
(Howard:)...when I told you
I was gonna be an astronaut.
What did you think was gonna happen?
Honestly? Sex, heh.
(Leonard:)- Howard.
- Do you realize what a big deal this is?
What an honor it is
to be chosen to go into space?